JASON NELSON

jasonfswd@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jason-n-84778a124/ https://github.com/jasondamion https://jasondesigns.net

Full Stack Web Developer

Full stack web developer continuously learning the new tech being applied in the technologic field today. Experienced with excellent client and project management skills. Dedicated to building customer loyalty and promoting win-win results for the company and the client. Action-oriented with strong ability to communicate effectively with technology, executive, and business audiences.

Technology Summary

Certifications: AWS Cloud Practitioner

Front-End: HTML5, BootStrap, CSS3, JQuery, Ajax, DOM Manipulation, Handlebars, Javascript, API's, React.JS **Back-End:** Node.JS, Angular.JS, Handlebars.JS, Express.JS, MySQL, Java, MongoDB, Sequelize/Mongoose

Software: Github, Git Version Control, Firebase, Git Bash, Command Prompt, FTP Client, AWS Console/CLI/SDK

Projects

Daycare Manager | Node.js, MySQL | Github

Full Stack Developer

Single-page web app for managing my church daycare.

- Incorporates Express.Js to host a local server to render the code on the laptop..
- Dynamically renders features and components using Handlebar.js with Sequelize.
- Utilizes Bootstrap, CSS, and SQL queries to retrieve the children and their timesheets.

Heroes Vs Heroes | API's | JSON Proxy | Github | Live

Back-End Developer

Single-page web app for estimating who would win in a fight between heroes.

- Uses the Superhero API to get stats for each superhero.
- Compares the stats and decides the winner based on a point system.
- Returns gifs from the Giphy API showing the winner.

Bamazon | Inquirer, MySQL | Github

Back-End Developer

Single-page web app for estimating who would win in a fight between heroes.

- Utilizes the CLI table module to show a table of products.
- Uses inquirer to get the customer order.
- Returns the table after the order is made.

Professional Experience

Domino's Pizza Dumont, NJ 2019-Current

Assistant Manager

- Coordinate daily customer service operations (e.g. sales processes, orders and payments)
- Monitor and maintain store inventory
- Handle complaints from customers
- Evaluate employee performance and identify hiring and training needs
- Supervise and motivate staff to perform their best

Domino's Pizza Dumont, NJ 2016 - 2019

Customer Service Representative

- Responsible for daily operational duties
- Training of new staff and managers
- Direct management of inbound call and order taking
- In charge of customer grievance resolution
- Directed shift peak times during management absence
- Responsible for pizza preparation

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM
Rutgers University, Jersey City, NJ, United States

2018-2019

AWS Training Program 2019-2019 AWS Learning Library, Online